https://www.nanniesoftherockies.com/privacy.php

Services
Contact Us!
home « privacy policy
Privacy Policy
Please Select
AlaskaAlabamaArkansasArizonaCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDistrict of ColumbiaDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIowaIdahoIllinoisIndianaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMassachusettsMarylandMaineMichiganMinnesotaMissouriMississippiMontanaNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNebraskaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNevadaNew YorkOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaVermontWashingtonWisconsinWest VirginiaWyoming
Privacy Statement, Practice and Policies
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available via a link from our homepage and at various points throughout our website. If you send us an electronic mail message that contains personal information we will only use this information to respond to your request. We may forward your message on to another department or agency in a better position to answer your question.
You have a right to review the information collected about you by this site. Contact the service provider to review your information.
Information We Collect
We are committed to helping match users who are seeking sitter or nanny services ("Seekers") to users who are providers of sitter or nanny services (" Providers"). Accordingly, we collect user submitted personally identifying information and other information specific to the services requested or provided. As part of providing you our services, we may obtain personal information from the following sources:
• Information you provide to us on forms that you enter on the Site or that you provide to us in writing.
• Information that you provide to us by telephone, such as when you contact our customer care department.
• Information we receive automatically when you visit our web site, such as Internet Protocol (IP) Address, type of browser and operating system used to access our site (“Netscape 4.7”, “Windows 2000”), date and time the user accessed out site, etc.
• Error conditions that may have occurred, including (under some circumstances) arguments which may have been supplied by the user to the program being run.
• Information from third parties, including verification services, payment processing services, and other online and offline sources. For example, this would include information we receive from a third-party verification service in response to a user requesting a background check on themselves. It would also include updated address or contact information that we might use to correct our records so that we can communicate with you more easily.
Registered users and Subscribers will also provide personal contact information including, but not limited to, name, telephone, email, and address information. Under no circumstances does SittersoftheRockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com allow for the anonymous registration of a Provider/sitter or parent.
The information we collect may include: first name, last name, city, state, address, ZIP code, phone, email address and other information specific to the service requested or provided. If you become a registered subscriber we may collect your credit card information and billing address. If you become a registered Care Provider, we may collect your date of birth, gender, company name (if applicable), and ZIP codes served. If you request a background check on yourself we may collect your Social Security Number. In addition, if you request a background check on yourself we may obtain criminal background information from a third-party verification service. Use of such a verification service is voluntary.
How We Use the Information We Collect
Sitters of the Rockies LLC nor Nannies of the Rockies LLC share, sell or rent the personal information of any registered user to any other company or organization. We do not share this information with outside unaffiliated parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to process a background check on such person. We do not share this information with unaffiliated outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We post babysitter or nanny candidates' qualifications and job-related information on our web site. We also post prospective job related information on our web site. We may inform babysitter or nanny candidates and prospective employers of each other's preferences, qualifications and potential working conditions. If you are a babysitter or nanny candidate or prospective employer of babysitters or nannies, you consent to these disclosures by use of our service or web site.
Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of SittersoftheRockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com, such as in a profile listing, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of SittersoftheRockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com.
User information collected by the Sitters of the Rockies LLC or Nannies of the Rockies LLC is the minimal data required to successfully complete a web transaction. We use contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
We may use your personal information to contact you, or have an independent third-party contact you in an effort to evaluate our service level and your satisfaction with our product. Any third-party organization acting as our agent or as an independent research firm will maintain the integrity of your personal information and may never share, sell or rent that information to any other company or organization.
Information collected automatically by our server is analyzed to help us understand how you use our web services and how we can improve our site to better meet your needs. This information is also used to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file created by a web site on your computer hard drive that contains unique information that the site can use to track such things as passwords, lists of pages you have visited, the date you last looked at a page, or identification of your session on the site.
Cookies stored are used to only to identify you to the site and make your use of the site more convenient for you.
Personal profile information you store on our site is used only by the site to complete accurate and useful database searches that you initiate or that have been initiated by another site user, per the terms of use, based on the preferences you have selected. You have the ability and the right to modify your preferences and personal information at anytime.
Data Security
The Sitters of the Rockies LLC and Nannies of the Rockies LLC take every precaution to protect the user's information. When a user submits sensitive information via the web, that information is protected both online and off-line.
When a form asks users to enter confidential information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Encryption.
We strive to protect user information off-line. Access to all user information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform necessary functions are granted access to this information. Sensitive data is stored in a secure format. While you may suspend or cancel your account at anytime, The Sitters of the Rockies LLC or Nannies of the Rockies LLC, for purposes of safety and security, will maintain a record of your account for a period of no less than two years from the date of your last access to the website.
Information Retention
To preserve the integrity of our databases, standard procedure calls for us to retain information submitted by members for an indefinite length of time. SittersoftheRockies.com and/or NanniesoftheRockies.com understands your submissions as consent to store all your information in one place for this indefinite length of time, if we so wish. If required by law, as is the case to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will nullify member information by erasing it from our database. We will also respond to written member requests to nullify account information. If you wish to make such a request, which requires us to verify your identity, or if you have any questions regarding this policy, contact SittersoftheRockies.com at info@sittersoftherockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com at NanniesofRockies@aol.com. SittersoftheRockies.com and/or NanniesoftheRockies.com are intended for people 18 or over. Our process is intentionally designed to identify children under 18 years of age. We have also made an effort to specifically limit SittersoftheRockies.com’s and/or NanniesoftheRockies.com’s appeal to people of age 18 and older. SittersoftheRockies.com and/or NanniesoftheRockies.com will not knowingly collect any information from children under 13. Also, by using this site, you do hereby represent and warrant that you understand and agree that all information submitted by you to Sittersoftherockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com becomes the property of SittersoftheRockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com and may be used in the sole discretion of SittersoftheRockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.
Links to Other Websites
Our web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that SittersoftheRockies.com or NanniesoftheRockies.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. The user is encouraged to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. We do NOT pass on any of your personal information to any other site you visit.
Updating Personal Information
We provide a way to correct or update the personal information provided to us by users. This can be done at the member PROFILE page. Only a registered user has the ability to subscribe to the service and/or change any of their own user information, including, but not limited to, their subscription status and account status.
Email Notification
We send all registrants email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive email information on services, promotions, and/or a newsletter. These emails are deemed to contain information important to the use of the website and are sent to all registered users.
We communicate with users to provide requested services and to respond to issues relating to users account(s) via email, phone, mail and/or SMS Text Messaging.
Questions
Visit our FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS page for detailed answers to the most commonly asked questions. For additional information use our CONTACT US form to send a SSL Encrypted message or write to us at:
Sitters of the Rockies LLC
PO Box 3097
Boulder, CO 80307
Phone: 303-499-2002
Fax: 303-499-2023
Email: info@sittersoftherockies.com
Nannies of the Rockies LLC
PO Box 3097
Elder Care (non-medical)
Radius (Miles)
10
25
50
100
All content © 1991-2020 by Nannies OF the Rockies and Coast to Coast Nannies LLC - All rights reserved.
